salvationsystem.com 2011-09-26

# Privacy Policy Statement

## 1\. How to contact us

This is the website of the Twitter Salvation System. The website and online training material and/or software are developed by Puppet String Marketing, unless otherwise stated. 

Our customer service telephone number is: 1-270-968-8540  

Our fax number is: (270) 968-8540 

Our business address:

Puppet String Marketing, LLC  
5715 Will Clayton # 7650  
Humble, TX 77338  
**USA**

Puppet String Marketing  
Suite 201, MBE Bandar Sunway, No. 10, Jalan 11/28A,   
Sunway Metro, Bandar Sunway,   
Petaling Jaya  
Selangor 46150   
**Malaysia**  

Should you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us:

[puppetstringmarketing@gmail.com](mailto:puppetstringmarketing@gmail.com) _or_[info@puppetstringmarketing.com](mailto:info@puppetstringmarketing.com)

## 2\. Our commitment to privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## 3\. The information we collect

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## 4\. The way we use information

**What do we use your information for?**

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify customers about updates to our website and is NOT shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, promotions, etc. However, you may opt-out at any time by (please enter the opt-out or unsubscribe process here. This may be something like clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of your emails. 

If you supply us with your postal address online, you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Customers who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online or urgent questions they have.

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated purposes not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

## 5\. Our commitment to data security

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Profile' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## 6\. How you can access or correct your information

Upon request, we provide our customers with access to all personally identifiable information (e.g., name, address, phone number) and transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we collect about them online.

Customers can access information that we collect about them by e-mailing us at the above address. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on 17th December 2008

## 7\. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at these addresses.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Email:

[puppetstringmarketing@gmail.com](mailto:puppetstringmarketing@gmail.com) _or_[info@puppetstringmarketing.com](mailto:info@puppetstringmarketing.com)

Phone: 1-270-968-8540  

Fax: (270) 968-8540 

Address:

Puppet String Marketing, LLC  
5715 Will Clayton # 7650  
Humble, TX 77338  
**USA**

Puppet String Marketing  
Suite 201, MBE Bandar Sunway, No. 10, Jalan 11/28A,   
Sunway Metro, Bandar Sunway,   
Petaling Jaya  
Selangor 46150   
**Malaysia**
